Guide to the Sir George Hubert Wilkins Papers
The Ohio State University. Byrd Polar and Climate Research Center Archival Program.
- Series II: Consultant Work: United States Military, 1936-1958; 9 cubic feet
  - Chart: Army Air Forces, Flight Control Command, Arctic Search and Rescue Squadron, Designation - Arctic Search and Rescue Squadron AAFFCC, May 26, 1943 (Box 11.1, Folder 13)
  - Chart: "Nomogram of Dry-Shade Atmospheric Cooling", Undated (Box 11.1, Folder 14)
  - Chart: "Effects upon men exposed to brief periods of extreme cold, US Antarctic Expedition 1939-1940" (Box 11.1, Folder 15)
  - Pencil Drawings of section of a sled, related correspondence and report, 1943 and Undated (Box 11.1, Folder 16)
  - Blueprints of Specifications: Sled/Toboggan, ca 1943 (Box 11.1, Folder 17)
  - Large pencil drawing of section of sled/toboggan, ca 1943 (Box 11.1, Folder 18)
  - Large pencil drawing of section of sled/toboggan, ca 1943 (Box 11.1, Folder 19)
  - Drawing of sled by A.H. Woodcock, ca 1943 (Box 11.1, Folder 20)
  - "Airplane Crash Fire Fighting Time - Temperature Tests": Laurinburg-Maxton Air Base, September 11-15, 1944 (includes photographs, charts, and diagrams), September, 1944 (Box 11.1, Folder 21)
  - "Efficiency Analysis - Quartermaster Items and Functions", Undated (Box 11.1, Folder 22)
  - Drawings: Tent Pentagonal, Undated (Box 11.1, Folder 23)
  - Tent Pattern: Probably for Consultant Work - US Military, Undated (Box OV-24, Folder 1)
- Series III: Correspondence, 1908-1958; 1.5 cubic feet
  The Correspondence series contains one and one-half cubic foot of material. It is primarily general correspondence and is not specific to any of the expeditions/trips or consultant work.
  - Correspondence, ca. 1908-1919 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    Includes: 1. Letters sent to parents from London 2. Bill from supply store (in French) 3. 4 issues of 'The Model Engineer and Electrician'
  - Correspondence, 1912 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    Includes: 1. Letters sent by Wilkins to his parents 2. Letters to/from Imperial Ottoman Embassy 3. letters of introduction from various organizations sent out prior to Wilkins' touring of The UK and European continent 4. Receipts from "Bought of George & A. Baker" 5. Address list / Business cards
  - Correspondence, 1913 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    Includes: 1. Letters to Parents 2. Letter from W.G. Gardine 3. Letter from Imperial Ottoman Embassy 4. Personal Note(planning for a birthday)
  - Correspondence, 1916 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    Includes: 1. letter from T.A. Welsh
  - Correspondence, 1917 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    Includes: 1. letters addressed to parents 2. a 1917 Censor's List, World War I images 3. Marathon Science Club event schedule
  - Correspondence, 1918 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    Includes: 1. letters addressed to mother 2. French photography permits
  - Correspondence, 1919 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    Includes: 1. Letter addressed to mother 2. concert program
  - Correspondence, ca. 1920s (Box 12, Folder 8)
    Includes: 1. Letters from The Guild of Former Pipe Organ Pumpers, Horlick's Malted Milk Corporation 2. 2-day schedule (10/18, 10/19) 3. unaddressed letter fragment regarding Amundsen 4. Telegram referencing Louis Alber 5. Personal notes, stationary, business card
  - Correspondence, 1920 (Box 12, Folder 9)
    Includes: 1. Correspondence with: Dorothy Stanley, a certain 'Hilda', a Major in the Australian Imperial Force, San Francisco chief of police, Vilhjamur Stefansson, Editor of Birmingham Post, Captain R.N. Hardy, Rolls-Royce
  - Correspondence, 1921 (Box 12, Folder 10)
    Includes: 1. Various invitations
  - Correspondence, 1922 (Box 12, Folder 11)
    Includes: 1. Correspondence with: mother, Aubrey Walk, Frank Wild 2. Invitation and theater program (in Russian)
  - Correspondence, 1923 (Box 12, Folder 12)
    Includes: 1. Correspondence with: Mother, E.E. Stuart Baker, E.W. Deming, Dorothy Stanley 2. Admission letter from Royal Meteorological Society (copy) 3. Poem 4.
  - Correspondence, 1924 (Box 12, Folder 13)
    Includes: 1. Correspondence with: Edgeworth David, Vilhjalmur Stefansson, Barens 2. Pamphlet, Australian Association for the Advancement of Science 3. Note about 'Stef's pomposity'
  - Correspondence, 1925 (Box 12, Folder 14)
    Includes: 1. Correspondence with: H.G. McCutchen, Royal Geographical Society 2. Invitation to event with Amundsen
  - Correspondence, 1926 (Box 12, Folder 15)
    Includes: 1. Correspondence with: British Museum of Natural History, Yogi Publication Society, Boy Scout Scoutmaster 2. Proposal for Membership with The Explorers Club with endorsements (copies) 3. Wilkins lecture schedule
  - Correspondence, 1927 (Box 12, Folder 16)
    Includes: 1. Correspondence with: American geographical Society (Joerg), North American Newspaper Alliance, A. Page Cooper 2. "A page of my Log Book Shows" 3. Document describing "Plan and Scope of Ligue Internationale Des Aviateurs"
  - Correspondence, 1928 (Box 12, Folder 17)
    Includes: Correspondence From: Oliver Baedwin, Anna Jarvis, Setre Kjeksfabrik, Burt McConnell, Wily Richards, Ralph Stacy 2. Unsigned, regarding book deal upon return from Antarctic flight
  - Correspondence, 1929 (Box 12, Folder 18)
    Includes: 1. Letter from Morris, regarding Gold Medal from Cuban Geographical Society
  - Correspondence, ca. 1930s (Box 12, Folder 19)
    Includes: 1. Correspondence with: Theodore Ash, Rachel Borovoy, James Edmund Boyack, 'Betty' 2. Telegram from Coast Guard, listing frequencies for Aklavaick Radio Station, Canada 3. Short list of Hungarian phrases 4. rough list, cost of supplies
  - Correspondence, 1930 (Box 12, Folder 20)
    Includes: 1. Correspondence with: Reginald (Baker, Simonds & co.), A.G. Beaman, John Borden, Chapman & Hall Ltd., Dejean, Frank A. Eaton, E.S. Evans, Marlo Field, Rudolph Haleth, Albert Lauries, T. Melvin Lee, Norsk Marconikompani 2. Lecture Schedule, Alber & Wickes 3. Train Schedule (Portland, Oregon) 4. "The Spirit of Adventure"
  - Correspondence, 1931 (Box 12, Folder 21)
    Includes: Correspondence with: 'Bert', Dr. Isaiah Bowman, Katharine M. Brown, Bryant, John Cudahy, Robert Gibbings, P. J. McDonnel, Joan Noel, Harold M. Sherman, H.N. Valden
  - Correspondence, 1932 (Box 12, Folder 22)
    Includes: Correspondence with: The Affiliated Lecture & Concert Association, Block, Brooklyn Edison Company Inc., G.W. Coplen, P.S. Duryee, Ellison-White Bureau, Emerson Bureau, Arthur Flury, Herbert H. Gowen, Cal Johnson, Hubert A. Kay, William J. Keating, Lieutenant A. Lewis, Robert C. Miller, Henry Moser, NBC Artists Service, H.R. Peat, Rotary Club of Victoria B.C., Royal Scottish Geographical Society, Antonio Hai Sanglai, Margaret Smith, Thomas G. Thompson, M.C. Turner, C.A. Tusch, William A. Wolf 2. Date Notice, April 21-22 3. Description of 'Fairbanks Great Circle Map', from US Department of the Interior 4. Chapter names list
  - Correspondence, 1933 (Box 12, Folder 23)
    Includes: 1. Correspondence With: H. Bornsen, Dr. Henry B. Bigelow, Boy Scouts of America, Guarantee Trust Company of New York, Right Rev. Monsignor T. King, Lewisham Private Hospital, R.R. Pritchard, Hubert Whittle, Woods Hole Oceanographic Institution 2. Letter to a 'Susan', from Lady Wilkins 3. Envelope with various invitations 4. test key
  - Correspondence, 1934 (Box 12, Folder 24)
    Includes: 1. Correspondence with: Callaghan, Elliots & Australian Drug Limited, Lincoln Ellsworth, Furness Lines, H.J. Hickey, A Leigh. Hunt, Invercargill, King, John Lane, E.C.M. Lousada, Mackee, New Zealand Antarctic Society, R.R. Pritchard, L.A. Quinn, John Seabrook, Stauffer, Udell, Welsh
  - Correspondence, 1935 (Box 12, Folder 25)
    Includes: 1. Correspondence with: Beaman, Gustavo M. Costabel, Furness Lines, Humberto Orrego Gautier, Ed. F. Gorski, Angel H. Huango, Miffington Krake, Clyde A. Nelson, Parva Domus Magna Quies Great General Assembly, H.J. Rahlves, L.U. Reavis, Jose M. Gomez Rebolledo, P.L. Young 2. Temporary Admission Report (customs, Canada) 3. US Customs Service forms (blank)
  - Correspondence, 1936 (Box 12, Folder 26)
    Includes: 1. Correspondence with: M.R. Brooks, Austin Byrne, A.M. Carey, Harold Chafey, Jessie R. Chamberlin, The City Club of New York, Cowles, W.C. Dreene, Barry Faris, The General Electric Company, Lauren M. Gibbs, A. Gordon-Firing, Arthur J. Gowan, L.O. Harnecker, William Randolph Hearst (copies), Ben Jacobson, Joery, H.W. MacDonald, J.C. McManemin Jr., William T. Meredith, J.T. Oliver, Aly B. Robinson, Jos. Robinson, Carl S. Saether, Emile Snyder, Vilhjalmur Stefansson, H.U. Sverdrup, W.C. Thompson 2. Invitation to Dinner with 'His Excellency and Madame Radoye Yankovitch 3. Invitation, Rafael Lovres, Club Vina del Mar 4. Envelope addressed to Wilkins at The City Club (56 West 44th St., NY City)
  - Correspondence, 1937 (Box 12, Folder 27)
    Includes: 1. Correspondence with: Abbot, American Philosophical Society, Australia House (Strand, London, W.C.2.), R.E.H. Baily, J. Erroll Boyd, Dr. L. Breitfuss, Henry M. Breitheall(sp), Bunnell, W. Atlee Burpee Jr., W.R. Butler, W.B. Caddell, Cyril Clemens, Dashwood & Partners, P.S. Conan Doyle, Drinker Biddle & Reath (law offices), N.B. Cousins, Lorene K. Fox, Victor Griffith, Louis J. Halle, Quincy Howe, Harold Gilbert, Reginald J. Iversen, A.H. Joelle, Dr. Breese Jones, G.V. Keeling, D.M. LeBourdais, Margaret Lesser, Victor E. Levine, Ernest Lilien, Little Ship Club, London Midland and Scottish Railway Company, Edward J. McCullen, James Mess, K. Frederick von Mohr, J.M. Philp, H.N. Potter, J. Robinson, Jeanie M. Stead, Vilhjalmur Steffanson, Arthur Hays Sulzberger, Sverdrup, N.R. Syme, E.A. Trefzger, University of Cambridge (dept. of Geography), W.H. Allen Sons & Company Limited, Watts Naval Training School, John N. Wheeler, B.M. Woolf, illegible 2. Telegraph, R.H. Fleet 3. American Geophysical Union, Eighteenth Annual Meeting Schedule 4. American-Russian Chamber of Commerce, Special Luncheon Meeting 5. American Philosophical Society program 6. Check addressed to Wilkins 7. Maps (transparencies)
  - Correspondence, 1938 (Box 12, Folder 28)
    Includes: 1. Correspondence with: Barrett Andrews (Street Railways Advertising Co.); Archiv fur Polarforschung; John Atkins (The Canadian Magazine); W.P. Balderston (Bendix Instrument Company Inc.); A.G. Beaman; A.H. Bennel (The Mutual Life Insurance Company of New York); 'Bert'; A. Boyd; W. Leigh Brintnell (Mackenzie Air Service Limited); Virginia Burdick (The American Russian Institute for Cultural relations with the Soviet Union, Inc.); Dale Carnegie (The Greater New York Fund); Cyril Clemens (International Mark Twain Society); Tullio Colsalvatico (Reale Accademia D'Italia); Angelo Crath Faruwacichov(sp); J. George Frederick (The Gourmet Society), Mark Hanna, Munson Havens (Chamber of Commerce), Newton D. Baker; V.M. Irwin; Louis Kiapa(sp) (The Cape Times); Gerald P. Lenox-Conygham (University of Cambridge, Dept. of Geodesy & Geophysics); Pepio Peuntices(sp); H.W. Perry; Windham Phinny; Pohjanpalo; Jon Reverant(sp); Robert Ripley; D.A. Rosoff (Amtorg Trading Corp.); Royal Geographical Society; Sherman(sp) (The City Club of New York); W. Spencer(sp); Vaeleiu(sp) Stavrakov; Alyemon Talmage(sp); Helen Templeman(sp); M.C. Turner (The Dixie Bureau); Watts Naval Training School; N. Yeenbleau(sp) 2. American Geophysical Union Calendar
  - Correspondence, 1939 (Box 12, Folder 29)
    Includes: 1. Correspondence with: African Consolidated Theatres Ltd.; Roger N. Baldwin (American Civil Liberties Union); A.H. Bennell (The Mutual Life Insurance Company of New York); Harry L. Bird (Louis and Brorby, Inc.); Earl W. Braga; F.A. Brockhaus; Walled S. Brawhead(sp); Cassidy; E.G. Conklin; Robert R. Hansen; Earl Hanson; Laura Ingalls; Hugo Levin; Marjorie Loeber (National Broadcasting Company Inc., Dramatic Auditions Committee); L.R. Macgregor (Office of The Australian Government Trade Commissioner In The USA); John W. Martin; The Mercury; D.D. Milne(sp); Geo. F. Nellist (Pan -Pacific Who's Who); Yoshikazu Okada (Imperial Fisheries Institute, Tokyo, Japan); Robert Ripley; T.E.M. Schumann; M. Lincoln Schuster (Simon and Schuster); Thomas R. Shipp; Lowell Thomas; E.A. Trefzger (Underwood Elliot Fisher Co.); The Union Bank of Australia Ltd.; Union of South Africa, Dept. of Irrigation, Meteorological Office; Frederick P. Vorbargh(sp) (National Geographic Society); Bradford Washburn (Appalachian Mountain Club); Ralph E. Weeks; Harold E. Wilson (NY World's Fair, Swift $ Co. Exhibit); Paul V. Winslow; Yom 2. Biography of Henry T. Blair 3. Book info, "Shall White Australia Fail?", Walter S. Bromhead 4. Newspaper clipping, "Sir H. Wilkins's Offer Declined", Copy
  - Correspondence, ca. 1940s (Box 12, Folder 30)
    Includes: 1.Correspondence with: Bane, Cousin Black, Standish Chard, Mere Cheshire, Division of Public Liaison, R.W. Hale, August Howard, Margery Leonard, Captain Odom, Noel G. Ogilive, Shainwald-Von-Ahlefeldt 2. Various letters addressed "Hello, hello" 3. Invitations 4. Diagram; "UN Dumbarton Oaks Proposals for the General International Organization" 5. text about sled dogs 6. Individual Equipment list 7. Notes/Diagrams/Maps 8. Operations manual for Zenish deluxe model 7G605 9. Pamphlet for 'Thoughts through Space'
  - Correspondence, 1940 (Box 12, Folder 31)
    Includes: 1. Correspondence with: Air France; E.W. Albrecht; John R. Austin; Birmingham Press; James Edmund Boyack; R.P. Breckenridge; S.B. Buckner; Raymond Leslie Buell; Allan Danere (Explorers Club); Earl Hansen; Robert R. Hansen; W.C. Jackman; Hugo Levin; Alexander MacLehose; Alick Mclean; F. H. McMahon; Chao. W. Morse (Dept. of Education, Binghampton, NY); Charlotte LAwrence Otimes; Joseph Robinson; The Saturday Review; Harold Sherman; Paul J. Spengler; John M. Sterling; Richard Taplinger; James Terrell; Ralph Shainwald Von-Ahlefeldt; H.W.W.; Wickes; 2. Member list and Inaugural Dinner program, Australian Society of New York
  - Correspondence, 1941 (Box 12, Folder 32)
    Includes: 1. Correspondence with: C. Irving Benson; P.W. Litchfield; John W. Pontius; C.S. Weatherholt 2. Fifth Annual Report, Australian-American Co-operation Movement
  - Correspondence, 1942 (Box 12, Folder 33)
    Includes: 1. Correspondence with: G.D. Babcock; City Club of New York; W.E. Cudlipp; Dominion Geodesist; Austin L.E. Gros; J. Edgar Hoover; W. George Huntingon; W. George Huntington; Noel J. Ogilvie; H. Chas. Rawlins; Dr. Vilhjalmur Stefansson; Chas Wilson(sp) (Dept. of Education, Binghamton, NY); Gene (Zenith Radio Corporation) 2. Special Anzac Day Issue, Haere-Mai Newsletter
  - Correspondence, 1943 (Box 12, Folder 34)
    Includes: 1. Correspondence with: M.P. Alpert; F. Sherman Buker (D. Appleton-Century Company); Jacques Chambrun; Fenley (Flushing, Long Island); Benjamin Franklin (Associated Executives Clubs, Inc.); Miller Freeman; Archibald Gilchrist; Geoffrey T. Hellman; Harry G. Letts (Army Air Forces); John K. Northrop; Lawrence C. Oertle; Joseph M. Price; Terrence M. Read (Spelman College); Alexander P. de Seversky; John F. Stanwell-Fletcher (US Army Forces, Central Canada); Donald B. Upham; Elsie Weil; Philip H. Zink (The Republic Stamping and Enameling Co.)
  - Correspondence, 1944 (Box 12, Folder 35)
    Includes: 1. Correspondence with: James. J. Beeg(sp); 'Winston' 2. Program, American Platform Conference 3. Notice of Annual Meeting of Stockholders, Jack Waite Mining company 4. Film Description, Eskimo Arts and Crafts 5. memo, comparing Russian vs F-3 suits
  - Correspondence, 1945 (Box 12, Folder 36)
    Includes: 1. Correspondence with: Dr. Alexander Bajkov; Phillips Carlin (Mutal Broadcasting Co.); G.E. Gustafson (Zenith Radio Corp.); Harry P. Harrison (The Redpath Bureau); William Herbert Hobbs; T.E. Hughes (Cleveland Diesel Engine Division); Olson; Jorma Pohjanpalo; John G. Prentiss (Zenith Radio Corp.); Joseph A. Sadony (Educational Research Laboratories); C.R. Teller (Lawrence & Teller); M.C. Turner (The Dixie Bureau)
  - Correspondence, 1946 (Box 12, Folder 37)
    Includes: 1. Correspondence with: Ralph S. von Ahlefeldt; 'Anne'; P. Neville Barnett; Thomas H. Bennett, Jr.; Dr. Briggs; Ralph E. Dunford (University of Tennessee); Orrin Dunlap, Jr. (Radio Corp. of America); Mrs. Charles T. Estes (The Cooperative Committee); Maurice Ewing (Columbia University); 'Gene', E.F. McDonald, Jr. (Zenith Radio Corp.); Robert R. Hansen; Charles Harrell; C.J. Hubbard (Massachusetts Institute of Technology); D. Hutchison (Hudson's Bay Company); Laurence Irving (Swarthmore College, Dept. of Zoology); Reginald J. Iversen (Institute of Radio Engineers, Board of Directors); Madeleine Juohy (Redpath Bureau); Ted Kavanaugh (Curtis Publishing Company); Edward M. Kirby; E.F. McDonald (Zenith Radio Corp.); John I. Moore; John W. Nason (Swathmore College); Culbert L. Olson; N.P. Pery (Columbia Pictures Pty. Ltd.); Loring Pickering; Jorma Pohjanpalo; George Palmer Putnam; Joseph Sadony (Educational Research Laboratories); Robert Schoendorf; Ray E. Shreck; C.R. Teller (U.S. Navy); The Wilson Ornithological Club; J. Wolodarsky (United Thermo-Stable Corp.); Philip N. Youtz; William B. Ziff 2. Letter addressed 'Hello, hello!' 3. Regarding establishment of meteorological stations in Canadian Arctic
  - Correspondence, 1947 (Box 12, Folder 38)
    Includes: 1. Correspondence with: The Australian Society of New York; Charles H. Babb; C.E. Backman (The Redpath Bureau); Alec. Bajkov; Richar Baron; Arthur Besser(sp); Meredith F. Burrill (US Department of the Interior, Board on Geographical Names); Standish Chard (Radio Productions, Inc.); Dr. Erling Christophersen (Norwegian Embassy); Harold T. Clark; Willard Collins; Deeg; Reverend W.L.S. Fleming (Scott Polar Research Institute); Fred; Theodore Fredenburgh (Duell, Sloan & Pearce, Inc.); Katharine Fuguet (The Grolier Society, Inc.); Robert R. Hansen; William H. Hobbs; Grace M. Humphrey; Edgar E. Guttenberg (Calvert Distillers Corp); Freda Kirchwey (The Nation Associates); Lauritz Liavaag; Peer Lovfald; Trevor Lloyd (Dartmouth College, Dept. of Geography); Louise P. McDowell (The Grolier Society, Inc.); Ernest McIver; Lionel C. Moise (Hearst Newspapers); Sidney Paige (The Joint Research and Development Board); Howard Prescott; Louis C. M. Reed (Circumnavigators Club); Finn Ronne; Joseph Sadony (Educational Research Laboratories); Isabel B. Smith (US Coast Guard); Donald Soochs(sp); S.H.K. Spurgeon (Australian Embassy); B.L. Straubel; Ernest Sullivan; H.U. Sverdrup; Lewis Eugene Thompson; 'Tom'; M.C. Turner (The Dixie Bureau); Alastain Walker; John W. Weigt (The Electric Storage Battery Company); O.W. Wells; John N. Wheeler (North American Newspaper Alliance, Inc.); M.E. White (Redpath Bureau); Mrs. Frank C. Williams (James River Woman's Club); Walter A. Wood (USA Embassy in Ottawa, Ontario, Canada); James W. Zarbock (Robert M. McBride & Co.); Zenith Radio Corp.; William B. Ziff (Ziff-Davis Publishing Co.) 2. Personal letters, illegible names 3. "Extracts from Letters Received from Scientific Institutions" 4. Programs for The American Geographical Society; The Los Angeles breakfast Club; 5. The Natural Science Courses (pamphlet) 6. "Specifications of Trawler 97", with blueprint 7. "Particulars of Amateur Communications -- R.A.R.E." 8. Sample questions and insturctions for a written test 9. "Engagement Schedule for Sir Hubert Wilkins"
  - Correspondence, January-June 1948 (Box 12, Folder 39)
    Includes: 1. Correspondence with: P.D. Baird (The Arctic Institute of North America); Greta(sp) Bates (The Oakland Forum); S. Russell Bridges (Alkahest Celebrity Bureau); Peter T. Byrne (Securities and Exchange Commission); A.M. Carey (Fortune); Standish Chard (Radio Productions Inc.); Willard Collins; Hawthorne Daniel; Paul H. Durrie; Irvine C. Gardner; R.W. Hale (The Edmonton Club); W.C. Hefferlin (Ray-Dox MFG. Co.); Ford Hicks (National Lecture Bureau, Inc.); Raymond J. Hock (Arctic Research Laboratory); Grace M. Humphrey (Humphrey Lecture Management); Julia E. Knitgen(sp) (The Woman's Club); George A. Liano (Smithsonian Institution); Rodney Maingot (F.R.C.S.); W.H. Middleswart (Dept. of the Army); T.M. Miller (The Canadian Club); H.F. Truman (Harold R. Peat, Inc.); George F. Pierrot (World Adventure Series); Milton Reynolds (Reynolds Pen Company); Harold M. Sherman; Thatare(sp); M.C. Turner (The Dixie Bureau); Marie Tremaine (Bibliography Project); Vancouver Board of Trade; John Wharrs(sp); J.F.M. Whiteley (National Defence College); J. Tuzo Wilson; J.G. Wilson(sp); W.A. Wood (Arctic Institute of North America); 2. National Lecture Management, and other pamphlets 3. Engagement Schedule 4. "Minutes of Meeting of Directing Committee, Bibliography and Roster Projects 5. Booking receipt for Mortgage Guarantee Building
  - Correspondence, July-December 1948 (Box 12, Folder 40)
    Includes: 1. Correspondence with: Harvey Agnew (Royal Canadian Institute); E. Maurice Bloch; 'Bob' (Reeve Aleutian Airways); Russel Bridges (Alkahest Celebrity Bureau); M.H. Burns; Cyril Clemens (Mark Twain Society); Henry B. Collins, Jr. (Arctic Institute of North America); Richard C. Darnell; L.H. Derrer; G. Vibert Douglas (Dalhousie University); Fairbanks; Richard F. Ferguson (Te Tabard Inn); James Finan (The Reader's Digest); R.W. Hale; F. Kenneth Hare (McGill University); Ford Hicks (National Lecture Bureau, Inc.); Horton Steel Works; August Howard (American Polar Society); Charles J. Hubbar; A. Innes-Taylor (U.S. Weather Bureau); Douglas N. Kendall (Photographic Survey Company Ltd.), Geological Air Survey; George H.T. Kimble (McGill University); Richard U. Light (The American Geographical Society); Litchfield (Goodyear Tire and Rubber Co.); Rodney Maingot (F.R.C.S.); Burt M. McConnell (The Explorer's Club); Robert E. McConnell; Clint Mcdade; John C. Metcalfe (National Lecture Management); John W. O'Malley; Grace Sims Peat; Morten P. Porsild; Fred A. Price; Florence C. Rawlings; H. Chas. Rawlins (Optimist Club); Lillian Riss (Harold R. Peat, Inc.); Harold E. Saunders (Navy Dept.); W.A. Shields (Canadian Cavalcade); Suzanne; M.C. Turner (The Dixie Bureau); L. Gahagan Walker; A.L. Washburn (Arctic Institute of North America); L. Waterman (Universal International Pictures); Philip N. Youtz (Scientific Continental Institute, Inc.) 2. Booking receipt, Mortgage Guarantee Building 3. American Polar Society Membership Report (List) 4. Pamphlets, including "Oyez! Habeas Crapus"
  - Correspondence, 1949 (Box 12, Folder 41)